and you don't worry about that later.
And most importantly, you're probably wondering,
since you two are handcuffed together,
how do you use the bathroom?
Oh, yeah.
Someone go in the bathroom?
Stop it.
I have to shower with this one.
Yeah, if you take it off at any point, the video's over.
Slide the handcuffs in there.
Wait, you guys look cool.
Boom.
Hey, she needs more sluck.
But what if she has to use the toilet?
Hey, hey.
Wait, I can't believe I'm in the same room as you're in now.
Yeah, and you kind of stuck with me.
Yeah.
Wait, am I stuck with you?
Oh gosh.
Actually, Susie has been through this kind of challenge
before.
You see, she lasted a hundred days in a room
with a complete stranger.
But this time, she's trapped with someone
she knows a little too well.
One thing to decide.
Do we even want to be eating together?
Oh, no.