Good morning. Good luck.
They really made this like prison.
At least you took cold.
Uncomfortable. Cold.
As always, we have made tons of cameras
monitoring their every move.
They're looking for everything that we're saying,
so anything that we say.
They're gonna get ideas.
Today was the first time that this cop
in this criminal have ever met.
We didn't know it yet,
but over the course of this video,
Ian and Linnie quickly became enemies.
There's gonna be stealing.
I am now the smuggling convict.
Bites.
I'm not religious.
It's an issue.
Right, I see that.
We're gonna need an EMT and even portray Linnie the snitch.
This is brutal.
Will they make it the entire hundred days?
Or will one of them screw the other?
All I wanna do is go home with all the money
and if I have to strangle a cop.
So...